== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Amy:)You know, with us living
together, maybe we could
(Amy:)think about having people over.
(Sheldon:)We have people
over all the time.
(Sheldon:)We have the maintenance people,
the pizza delivery man...
(Sheldon:)...that UPS driver
who feels the need to ask
(Sheldon:)how parts of me are hanging.
(Amy:)You know what I meant.
(Sheldon:)All right, fine.
(Sheldon:)Let's say that
(Sheldon:)we were to entertain people.
(Sheldon:)What type of gathering
did you have in mind?
(Sheldon:)Huh? A meal? Lunch?
(Sheldon:)Brunch? Dinner?
(Sheldon:)Afternoon tea?
A formal tea? Hmm?
(Sheldon:)Is it a party?
And if so, what kind of party?
(Sheldon:)Is it a cocktail party?
(Sheldon:)A Tupperware party?
Ooh, yeah--
is it a surprise party?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I hope it's not
(Sheldon:)a West Coast party,
'cause according to
(Sheldon:)the man on the radio,
a West Coast party don't stop.
(Amy:)I'm sorry I mentioned it.
(Sheldon:)Oh, don't be.
You get your hopes up,
(Sheldon:)I knock them down.
That's called teamwork.